# Rebeca Guedes

**UI/UX Designer** 

rebecatcmg@gmail.com
604-499-5875
linkedin.com/in/rebeca-guedes
github.com/rebecatschiedel

-

Working as a baker, I enjoyed creating products that would bring joy to my clients.

As a web developer, I discovered my ability in solving problems.

As a UX designer I use my previous experiences, allied with the User Centered Design concept, to empathize with the user and create a functional product.

# SKILLS

#### Tools

Figma, Invision, POP App, Zeplin

## **UX Methods**

User Research, Usability Testing, Task flows, Wireframing, Prototyping, Responsive Web Design

### **Programming**

HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, React, NodeJS, Git, GitHub, NextJS

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Baker | The Original Cupcakes**

DEC 2020 - PRESENT, VANCOUVER, BC

- Add unique recipes to the menu with great response from repeat clients.
- Demonstrate punctuality and organization by routinely completing a great number of orders under tight deadlines, guaranteeing quality.
- Successfully maintain strong relationships with colleagues, management and customers.

### Co-Founder and CEO | Vóia Biscoitos Caseiros

JUN 2014 - 2020, BRASÍLIA, BRAZIL

- Founded a small cookie business that later, with three other partners, grew into a small food industry specialized in healthy food for people with allergies.
- Developed original and tasty recipes, ensuring quality and consistency were exceeded.
- Trained the team with the new technologies and daily routines to optimize production.

#### **EDUCATION**

## BrainStation | Diploma Candidate, User Experience Design

JUL 2021 - SEP 2021, VANCOUVER, CA

## ComIT | Certificate, NodeJs

JAN 2021 - APR 2021, VANCOUVER, CA

# Harvard University | Certificate, CS50x Introduction to CS

DEC 2020, ONLINE

#### **PROJECTS**

## Web Dev Path (<a href="https://webdevpath.co/">https://webdevpath.co/</a>) | Front-End Developer

SEP 2020 - PRESENT, Volunteer

JavaScript, NextJs, CSS, Mailchimp

- Web Dev Path is a team of professional women with a web development background that aim to provide a comprehensive path for people who seek to begin their web development journey.
- The project next steps can be followed here: https://github.com/MarianaSouza/web-dev-path/projects/1.